Hi guys, I'm Mary Mosman. I'm your instructor
for the course this semester.  I just wanted to say hello before class starts
and let you kinda see who I am. So I am one of the full time
instructors at HTC, so feel free to reach out to me if you have
questions about our program or different classes. Um.
prerequisites, which order you should take classes in, when they might be
offered, general things like that. In addition to, of course, if you have questions
about this particular class, your assignments and things that you're working on.
So my office hours are posted on the syllabus. Feel free to
stop in, in-person. Um. You can also do
online meetings as well, so there are some preferred times for that
listed in the syllabus, but as long as you set something up with me in advance, and that works
for both of our schedules, I'm pretty flexible. I do ask though that
you try to set that up with me at least a day in advance, and for the weekends
um make sure you set up a time with me before 5 o'clock on Friday.
So that I can know my schedule for the weekend as well.
It works pretty well to do the online appointments.  We can do a
video meeting kinda like this where we can talk through somethings.
Um or we can do a screen share session. So if
you're working on an assignment, where it's more helpful to be looking at what you're
doing, we can do that too. And kinda talk through what you're working
on, how it's turning out, you know if things are behaving the way you expect
we can kind of interactively go through that, just like if we were in-person.
So I do encourage you to take advantage of this.  I don't want
you to feel like you're alone in the course. I'm here to help you. You just need to reach out to me
and let me know that you need some help.
You can also feel free to hit me up if you have questions about, um
what it's like to actually work as a developer out there in industry.
I do have 15 years plus, really, of experience
before I started here teaching full-time, so I've worked of
companies around the Twin Cities area. Um My background is in
Web Development with Java, JavaScript,
HTML, CSS, things like that.  Of course I've worked with databases too.
So feel free, if you've got questions about what it's like to
work out there, if you wanna talk about the job market. Um. Things
like that, feel free to hit me up for questions like that as well.
You can also connect with on LinkedIn, I do have an
HTC CCIS alumni group out there. It's a pretty cool community
We've occasionally had Happy Hours and I post job
postings and things like that out there for the group as well. Um
It is an alumni group, so you want to hit me up to get in the group as you're about
to graduate, um, but you can certainly connect with me on
LinkedIn in the mean time as well.
So you might also here that I like to game, and that would be true.
Um Computer games mostly, but board games are cool too.
I do have a Steam group out there, so if you too like to game
you should let me know and I would be more than happy to add you to our Steam
group that is specifically for HTC CCIS students
Um I don't play so many games myself over
the semester. You guys actually keep me quite busy. But the group
is really more about getting to know other students that have similar
interests, making some new friends, and just enjoying your free time.  So
if you're interested, send me your Steam name and I would be more
than happy to add you to the Steam group.